Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Jack Peters Papers, 1965-1989 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Jack Peters papers 1965-1989 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company.
41 linear feet Extent: 30,750 Items
The J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT), founded in 1864, is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. Jack Peters worked at JWT 31 years and served as Chief Operating Officer and President of JWT-USA (1984-1987) and JWT-Worldwide (1986-1987). The Jack Peters Papers span the years 1965-1989 and document Peters' career, especially his role in JWT's international offices, and with the Ford Motor Company advertising account. The collection includes general files related to JWT policies, procedures and personnel, advertising research reports, correspondence files, campaign proofs and launch materials, files related to media campaign strategies, presentation notes and scripts. The collection also contain marketing plans, evaluations and reports for a number of JWT's domestic and international offices, including Argentina, Canada, South Africa as well as offices in Europe and Asia. Represented clients include Eastman Kodak, Ford, Goodyear, Kellogg, Kraft, Miller beer, Twentieth Century Fox, Unilever, and Warner-Lambert.
RL.00738
Language: Material in English, German, Japanese, Spanish
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is restricted.
Files relating to personnel records are closed for 25 years from the date of the individual employee's death, or 40 years from the date of termination if the date of death cannot be determined.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Jack Peters Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1993.
Biographical Note
Chronology List
1931 Aug. 5 Born John Edwards Peters, Highland Park, Ill.
1952-1954 U.S. Army, Intelligence Division.
1956 B.S. in Business, Miami (Ohio) University.
1956 Joined JWT as Account Manager.
1972 Senior Vice President of JWT-USA and JWT-London.
1975 Executive Vice President and Account Director of JWT-USA in the New York office.
1977 Graduated from the Advanced Management Program, Harvard University.
1980 Vice Chairman of JWT-USA.
1984-1987 President and Chief Operating Officer of JWT-USA.
1986-1987 President and Chief Operating Officer of JWT-Worldwide.
1987 Dismissed from JWT, following a failed buy-out attempt, and subsequently retired.
1993 Aug. 5 Died, Greenwich, Conn.
After Leaving JWT, Peters ran an aviation company in Westchester, Conn.; practiced scuba diving (resulting in 200 dives in the Caribbean and Pacific Oceans); and served memberships in the American Bonanza Society and the American Soaring Society. On his birthday in 1993, Peters was shot and killed by a family friend while swimming at his home in Greenwich, Conn.
Collection Overview
The Jack Peters Papers span the years 1965-1989 and document Peters' career, especially his role in JWT's international offices, and with the Ford Motor Company advertising account. The collection includes general files related to JWT policies, procedures and personnel, advertising research reports, correspondence files, campaign proofs and launch materials, files related to media campaign strategies, presentation notes and scripts. The collection also contain marketing plans, evaluations and reports for a number of JWT's domestic and international offices, including Argentina, Canada, South Africa as well as offices in Europe and Asia. Represented clients include Eastman Kodak, Ford, Goodyear, Kellogg, Kraft, Miller beer, Twentieth Century Fox, Unilever, and Warner-Lambert.
Collection Arrangement
The collection is arranged into 11 series: Administrative Files; Client Files; Correspondence and Memoranda; International Offices; Meetings; New Business; Personnel Files; Reports; Subsidiaries; Writings and Speeches; and Oversize Materials. Administrative Files contains general memoranda, correspondence, policy information, and other files related to the organization and administration of JWT domestic and international offices, as well as to company policies on television and print media. Client Files contains correspondence, proofs, presentation notes and scripts, campaign ideas and clippings related to various JWT-USA and international clients, and especially the Ford Motor Company. Correspondence and Memoranda contains correspondence primarily between Jack Peters and various JWT employees, as well as general JWT office memoranda. International Offices contains correspondence, meeting reports, travel documentation, presentation files, audit information, information on features of various markets in specific regions, as well as general administrative memoranda for JWT's international offices. Meetings contains charts, presentation scripts, memoranda and logistical information, and notes pertaining to various JWT meetings and general advertising events. New Business contains scripts, plans, meeting files, and research related to JWT new accounts prospects, including scripts of general agency presentations, marketing and acquisitions plans, and new business reports from JWT regional domestic offices. Personnel Files includes materials on JWT personnel organization and management, employee biographies, transfers and statistics, as well as files on individual salaries, benefits and loans. Reports contains charts and prose reports covering topics such as advertising techniques, research, media, industries, and demographics. Also includes annual reports and operations reviews documenting the performance of various aspects of the JWT-USA's financial and organizational performance. These reviews include billings, expenditures, and profits, salaries, personnel, specific clients, and the company's public relations in the respective past year. Subsidiaries contains contracts, monthly statements, correspondence notes, charts, minutes, and other documents pertaining to JWT's domestic and European subsidiaries. Writings and Speeches contains scripts and notes relating to presentations and speeches given by Jack Peters and other JWT employees, primarily on JWT initiatives and status. Oversize Materials contains large-format items removed from previous series. Includes several proofs from Ford campaigns in various countries.
Subject Headings
Peters, Jack (John Edwards), 1931-1993; J. Walter Thompson Company; J. Walter Thompson Company -- History; Eastman Kodak Company; Ford Motor Company; Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company; Kellogg Company; Kraft Foods Company; Miller Brewing Company; Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation; Unilever (Firm); Warner-Lambert Company; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising agencies -- Argentina -- Buenos Aires; Advertising agencies -- Asia; Advertising agencies -- Europe; Advertising agencies -- Canada; Advertising agencies -- South Africa; Advertising executives -- United States; Advertising executives -- Europe; Advertising -- Research -- Europe; Advertising -- Research -- United States; Marketing research -- Europe; Marketing research -- United States; Proofs; Reports; Speeches; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Related Material
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center of the J. Walter Thompson Company Archives:
Account Files Collection
Biographical Information
Rena Bartos Papers
Arnold Grisman Papers
Don Johnston Papers
Bertram Metter Papers
W. Lee Preschel Papers
Frankfurt Office. Harry Clark Papers
Frankfurt Office. Denis Lanigan Papers
Contents of Collection
- Administrative Files, 1979-1987, (9 boxes)
  Contains general memoranda, correspondence, policy information, and other files related to the organization and administration of JWT domestic and international offices, as well as files related to company policy on television and print media. Also includes files related to special events, gifts and JWT contributions to various charities. Items are arranged alphabetically, with original folder titles maintained.
  - Administrative costs, 1982-1986 (Box 1)
  - Advertising Age rankings, 1985-1987 (Box 1)
  - Advertising Management Group files, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Agency billing information, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Agency performance evaluations format, 1981-1982 (Box 1)
  - Apartments, 1982-1986 (Box 1)
  - Archives policy, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Atlanta office, real estate, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Audiovisual expense forms, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Audits, general, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - Board members' photos, circa 1985 (Box 1)
  - Budgets, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Budget proposal, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Capital budgets, 1985-1986, (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Captive program, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Clippings, Advertising Age, 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Computers, 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Consultancy, 1982-1986 (Box 1)
  - Consumer Research Department, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Contributions
    - General, 1986 (Box 1)
    - Association for the Help of Retarded Children, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
    - Cerebral Palsy campaigns, 1984-1986 (Box 1)
    - New York Chamber of Commerce, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Coopers-Lybrand financial consultants, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Corporate Art Program, 1981-1986 (Box 2)
  - Corporate Committee, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Creative
    - Atlanta office, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Awards, 1979-1985 (Box 2)
    - Library, 1984-1986 (Box 2)
    - New York Office, 1984-1986 (Box 2)
    - San Francisco Office, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Deferred Retirement Income Agreement (DRIA), 1981-1984, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Domestic leases, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Donovan Computers, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Events
    - Boys Club of America Dinner, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Bucky Buchanan Retirement Dinner, 1985 Dec. 2 (Box 2)
    - Cerebral Palsy Gambling Gala, 1986 Nov. 14 (Box 2)
    - Dinners, general, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
    - Harvard Business School International Dinner, 1984 Apr. 11 (Box 2)
    - Leatherneck Ball (Box 3)
      - 1985 Mar. 29 (Box 3)
      - 1986 Apr. 11 (Box 3)
    - Thurman Munson Awards Dinner, 1986 Jan. 27 (Box 3)
    - National Football Hall of Fame Dinner
      - 1983 Dec. 6 (Box 3)
      - 1986 Dec. 9 (Box 3)
    - Navy League Anniversary Dinner
      - 1985 Nov. 6 (Box 3)
      - 1986 Nov. 5 (Box 3)
    - Jackie Robinson Awards Dinner and Dance, 1986 Mar. 31 (Box 3)
    - Granger Tripp retirement Dinner, 1984 Dec. 12 (Box 3)
  - Expense accounts, 1983-1985, (3 folders) (Box 3)
  - Financial, 1985-1987, (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - Financial plan, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Gifts (Box 4)
    - General, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Christmas gifts, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
    - Gift catalogs, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous gifts, 1984-1986, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Incentive plan, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Income and billings, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
  - JWT Group policies and procedures, 1985-1986 (Box 4)
  - JWT historical information, 1982-1986 (Box 4)
  - JWT organizational structure, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Management Information Services (MIS), 1985-1986 (Box 4)
  - Management Reference Center, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Manager and Creative Director, U.S. administration photographs, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Marketing Committee, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Media
    - General media file, 1984-1986, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Black media, 1982-1986 (Box 5)
      [Some items removed to oversize.]
    - Cable, 1982 (Box 5)
    - Chicago media file, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Commercial and print production, 1984-1986 (Box 5)
    - Competitive media, 1986 (Box 5)
    - Current spot media, 1985-1987, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - In-house spot system, 1985 (Box 5)
    - Los Angeles, entertainment division, 1984-1987 (Box 5)
    - Music, 1984-1986 (Box 6)
    - Spot buying, 1983-1985, (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - Spot buying unit, 1984-1986 (Box 6)
    - TV production, universities, 1985 (Box 6)
    - U.S. Core Media, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Merger information, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Mission statements, 1981-1985 (Box 6)
  - New York Art Studio, 1986 (Box 6)
  - New York State Tax project, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Number of offices, 1983-1985 (Box 6)
  - Operating policies, 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Organizational and Systems Assessment, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Policy and procedures, 1980-1986, (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Policies, Procedures and Statements Manual, 1986 (Box 7)
  - Press
    - General, 1983-1986 (Box 7)
    - John Naisbitt, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Publicity, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Public relations, 1983-1986 (Box 7)
  - Quality Control Committee, 1980-1984 (Box 7)
  - Real estate
    - General files, 1984-1986 (Box 7)
      [Includes 1984 Domestic Lease Update.]
    - Chicago Office, 1984-1987, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 7)
    - Chicago Office, 1984-1987 (continued), (2 of 2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Detroit Office, 1980-1986, (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Los Angeles Office, 1984 (Box 8)
    - San Francisco Office, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Washington, D.C. Office, 1984, 1986 (Box 8)
      [Includes photographs pertaining to 1984 location controversy.]
  - Research, 1984 (Box 8)
    [Includes Advertising Agency Reputation Survey.]
  - Revised capital budget format, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Sales promotion, 1985 (Box 8)
  - San Francisco, office space, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Securities Exchange Commission
    - Appearance, 1980-1984 (Box 8)
    - Quarterly Report, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Service and facilities, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Skills Inventory Database, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Standard Operating Procedures, Formal Reporting Requirements, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Summer 1984 t-shirts and tote bags (Box 8)
  - Thompson Achievement Awards Program (TAAP) / Management Incentive Plan (MIP) plans, 1980-1985 (Box 9)
  - Vendor file, 1984 (Box 9)
- Client Files, 1965-1987 and undated, (38 boxes)
  Contains correspondence, proofs, presentation notes and scripts, campaign ideas and clippings related to various JWT-USA and international clients, and especially the Ford Motor Company. Also includes information, clippings and notes related to situations in particular international markets. Items pertaining to JWT clients in general have been grouped into the General Files subseries. Items are arranged alphabetically first by client, then by location, with original folder titles maintained.
  - General Files
    Includes files pertaining to general JWT client policies, general presentations not specific to a client, as well as JWT client lists.
    - Atlanta Office accounts, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Case histories, undated (Box 9)
    - Chicago
      - Accounts, 1986 (Box 9)
      - Trip file, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Client compensation, 1984-1985, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Client compensation draft-outline, undated, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Client Compensation Handbook, 1985 (Box 9)
    - Client conflicts, 1984, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Client Contact List, 1986 Feb. 14 (Box 9)
    - Client lists, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Los Angeles account file, 1984-1986 (Box 10)
    - Multinational clients
      - General files, 1984-1986, (2 folders) (Box 10)
      - General files, 1984-1986, (2 folders) (Box 10)
      - Business Building Program, 1984 (Box 10)
      - Global Marketing...And One Way We Can Prosper From It, 1984 (Box 10)
      - Multinational meeting, 1985 Sept. 11 (Box 10)
      - Review of Thompson Multinational Client Organization Needs and Opportunities, 1983 (Box 10)
      - What Is Multinationality? Can It Be Cured?, 1983 (Box 10)
      - World Agency Competitive Review, 1985 (Box 11)
      - 1984 Retention and Growth Plans for Multinational Accounts, 1983 (Box 11)
    - North American Client List, 1986 (Box 11)
    - San Francisco accounts, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
    - Top 20 Worldwide Clients, 1983, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Washington, D.C. accounts, 1984-1986 (Box 11)
  - Activision, 1984 (Box 11)
  - American Gas Association, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - American Stores
    - General files, 1984 (Box 11)
    - Presentation, undated (Box 11)
  - Arrowhead Waters, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Atlantic Council, proposal, 1986 (Box 11)
  - Bacardi (London), 1983-1984 (Box 11)
  - Baskin-Robbins, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Beatrice Foods, 1985 (Box 11)
  - Bellsouth Mobility, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Black & Decker (London), 1983-1984 (Box 11)
  - Burger King (Germany), 1981-1985 (Box 11)
  - Burger King (U.S.A.) (Box 12)
    - General files, 1984-1986 (Box 12)
    - July 4 New York Celebration, undated (Box 12)
  - Carnation/Nestle, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Champion, 1982-1986 (Box 12)
  - Chevron (International), 1982-1984 (Box 12)
  - Chevron (U.S.A.)
    - General files, 1984-1986 (Box 12)
    - Executive update, 1985 (Box 12)
    - New York meeting, 1986 (Box 12)
    - Trip file, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Coke, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Computerland (Tokyo), 1984 (Box 12)
  - Computerland (U.S.A.), 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Continental Airlines, 1986 (Box 12)
  - De Beers (International)
    - General files, 1982-1985 (Box 12)
    - Fee information, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Diet Centers, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Dole, 1985-1986 (Box 12)
  - Dollar Rent-A-Car, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
  - Emery, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Entertainment Channel, New Approach presentation, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Firestone
    - Final letters and memos, 1971 (Box 13)
    - Presentation, 1969, (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Fisher-Price, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Ford (Argentina)
    - General files, 1979-1983 (Box 13)
    - Argentina situation, 1979-1981 (Box 13)
  - Ford (Argentina, Manila), general files, 1980 (Box 13)
  - Ford (Asia Pacific), general files, 1980-1984, (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Ford (Brazil), general files, 1982-1984 (Box 13)
  - Ford (Britain), general files, 1975-1983, (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Ford of Europe
    - General files, 1970-1983, (1-7 of 10 folders) (Box 14)
    - General files, 1970-1983, (8-10 of 10 folders) (Box 15)
    - Agency Evaluations, 1981-1982, (3 folders) (Box 15)
    - Audit information, 1982, (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Background file, 1982 (Box 15)
    - Beating a Down Economy, undated (Box 15)
    - Budget, 1972 (Box 16)
    - Caldwell presentation, 1983 Aug. 9 (Box 16)
    - Charts, 1983 (Box 16)
    - Client Retention Reports, 1980-1982 (Box 16)
    - Communication of Needs, 1982-1983, (2 folders) (Box 16)
    - Contemporary Marketing Within a Mass Environment, 1982 (Box 16)
    - Current Image Planning, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
    - Discussion, 1982 May 28 (Box 16)
    - Escort marketing, 1975 (Box 16)
    - ESO Carline Budget recommendation, 1983 (Box 16)
    - ESO and FOE Client Retention Reports, 1980-1983 (Box 16)
    - European Supervisors Meeting, 1983 Dec. 13 (Box 16)
    - Evaluation, 1982 Dec. 9 (Box 16)
    - Evaluation sessions, 1982 Aug. 17 (Box 16)
    - Fee, 1982 (Box 17)
    - Financial Operating Review, 1982 Oct. 26 (Box 17)
    - Ford Division Advertising, 1983 (Box 17)
    - Ford Image in Continental Europe, 1983 (Box 17)
    - Ford Image in Europe, 1983, (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Ford Image in Europe background materials, 1983, (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Ford Image files, 1983 (Box 17)
    - Ford Image presentation, correspondence and supporting material, 1983 (Box 17)
    - General presentation, 1982 May (Box 19)
    - Good Sense presentation, 1974 (Box 19)
    - Image project, 1983, (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Incoming, 1983-1986 (Box 19)
    - International, 1980 (Box 19)
    - Don Johnston / Walter Hayes file, 1983 (Box 19)
    - June pitch, 1983 (Box 19)
    - June 1983 presentation materials, 1983 (Box 19)
    - JWT Agency Evaluation, 1982 Dec. 9 (Box 19)
    - JWT Positioning Paper, 1983 Apr. 29 (Box 19)
    - May Lutz meeting, 1979-1983 (Box 19)
    - Manager's Monthly Assessments, 1982-1983 (Box 19)
    - Meeting, 1983 June 20 (Box 19)
    - Meeting files, 1983 (Box 19)
    - 1982 move, 1982-1983 (Box 19)
    - More Good News Advertising Guide, 1974 (Box 19)
    - Operations presentation, 1982 July (Box 19)
    - Organizational meeting, 1983 Sept. 7 (Box 19)
    - Jack Peters file, 1975 (Box 19)
    - Planning, 1983 (Box 19)
    - Positioning the 1983 Fords, 1982 (Box 19)
    - Presentation, 1981 (Box 19)
    - Presentation, working file, 1982 (Box 19)
    - Recommended Operational Advertising Procedures, 1974 (Box 19)
    - Recommended Operational Advertising Procedures, revised, 1974 (Box 20)
    - Reorganization and transfer, 1974 (Box 20)
    - Sierra launch meeting, 1982 July 19 (Box 20)
    - Sierra test launch, 1983 (Box 20)
    - Speeches, undated (Box 20)
    - Story of Ford in Europe, 1983 (Box 20)
    - Three Year Plan presentation, 1982, (2 folders) (Box 20)
  - Ford (Germany)
    - General, 1974-1980, (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - General, economic, 1983 (Box 20)
    - First Thoughts for Frankfurt Group Discussion, 1979 (Box 20)
    - Frankfurt, general files, 1985-1986 (Box 21)
    - Goeudevert meeting, 1983 Oct. 6 (Box 21)
    - Initiative Action Program, 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - JWT: The Agency, 1984 (Box 21)
    - Marketing meeting, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Marketing programs, 1984 (Box 21)
    - New German, 1984 (Box 21)
    - Presentation, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Project information, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Short Term Action Plan, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Status Reports, 1978, 1982, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 21)
    - Status Reports, 1978, 1982 (continued), (2 of 2 folders) (Box 22)
  - Ford (International)
    - General files, 1981-1986, (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Compensation, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Erika presentation, 1980 Mar. (Box 22)
  - Ford (Japan)
    - General files, 1979-1983 (Box 22)
    - Corporate
      - General corporate, 1982 (Box 22)
      - Basic Thoughts and Recommendations for Ford Corporate Campaign in Japan, 1982 Apr. 29 (Box 22)
    - Ford Takes on the Japanese, 1982 (Box 22)
    - Japan situation, 1981-1982 (Box 22)
  - Ford (Latin America)
    - Bonifactions, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
    - JWT and Ford in Latin America, 1981 Feb. 3 (Box 22)
    - Latin American Supervisors Conference, 1981 Apr. 23-24 (Box 22)
  - Ford (London)
    - Capri II, Selling Ideas, 1973 (Box 22)
  - Ford (Melbourne) (Box 23)
    - General files, 1981-1983 (Box 23)
  - Ford (Philippines)
    - General files, 1979-1983 (Box 23)
  - Ford (Singapore)
    - Meeting, 1980-1981 (Box 23)
  - Ford (South America)
    - General files, 1981-1985 (Box 23)
  - Ford (Spain)
    - General files, 1982 (Box 23)
  - Ford (Sweden)
    - New York meeting, 1983 Oct. 4 (Box 23)
  - Ford (Switzerland)
    - Marketing strategy, 1972 (Box 23)
  - Ford (Sydney)
    - 1979-1983 (Box 23)
  - Ford (U.S.A.)
    - Advertising Review, 1987 (Box 23)
    - Agreement of Terms, 1980-1983, (4 folders) (Box 23)
    - American Road campaign, 1965 (Box 23)
    - Approved Vendor List, circa 1979, 1981, (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - Audits (Box 24)
      - Audit information, 1978-1983, (5 folders) (Box 24)
      - Audit material, 1983 (Box 24)
      - Audit Report, Detroit, 1983 (Box 24)
      - Audit Report, New York, 1982 (Box 24)
    - Backup and FDAF, 1985-1986 (Box 24)
    - Bonifaction, 1983 (Box 24)
    - Benton meetings
      - Meeting files, 1980, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 24)
      - Presentation, 1979 (Box 24)
    - John Betti meeting, 1985 Dec. 5 (Box 25)
    - Bourke meeting, 1979 (Box 25)
    - Business Week interview, 1980 (Box 25)
    - Philip Caldwell meetings
      - Briefing, 1979 (Box 25)
      - Meeting files, 1982-1983 (Box 25)
      - Presentations, 1980-1982, (5 folders) (Box 25)
      - Presentation boards, 1979 July 25 (Box 25)
      - Presentation boards, 1979 July 25 (Box 25)
    - California Project, 1983 (Box 25)
    - California Vs. Total U.S. New Car Buyers, 1983 (Box 25)
    - Company Review, 1984 (Box 25)
    - Compensation, 1976-1983, (5 folders) (Box 26)